Gerry Mulligan Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Music (Box 1-148, 160)
  - Noblese
    - Part (bass, drums), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 115)
    - Lead sheets, For Ray Noble (Box-folder 19/14)
    - Lead sheets, From studio session with Scott Hamilton for the recording Soft lights and sweet music (Box-folder 19/17)
  - Nobody else but me
    - Part (piano), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 114)
    - Part (bass, drums), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 115)
    - Lead sheet, On folder: Chords for arrangement, for Q and others (Box-folder 64/3)
  - North Atlantic Run / Rocker Suite
    - Score; sketch score (orchestra) (Box-folder 141/4)
    - Score (orchestra) (Box-folder 141/3)
    - Score (orchestra) (Box-folder 77/2)
    - Parts for 3rd movement (orchestra), On folder: Copy for Jack Elliott (Box-folder 79/2)
    - Parts for 3rd movement (orchestra), Tom Fay arrangement (Box-folder 79/1)
    - Parts (orchestra), On folder: Used at Concordia 1/91; NSO Washington DC, 3/91 (Box-folder 78/2)
    - Part (piano), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 114)
    - Part (bass, drums), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 115)
    - Miscellaneous parts (Box-folder 13/4)
  - Northbound Drive
    - Sketch for 5 horns, Incomplete (Box-folder 50/1)
  - Nolstalgia in Times Square
    - Lead sheets, On folder: GM parts, Kelly and Mike's tunes (Box-folder 67/7)
  - Not mine
    - Score (strings), Julian Lee arrangement for the 1965 recording Feelin' good (Box-folder 117/5)
    - Parts (strings), Julian Lee arrangement for the 1965 recording Feelin' good (Box-folder 4/5)
    - Parts (strings), Julian Lee arrangement for the 1965 recording Feelin' good (Box-folder 4/13)
  - Now and again
    - Score; parts (Concert Jazz Band), Page 1 of score is missing (Box-folder 119/4)
  - Now and then
    - Score; parts (Concert Jazz Band), Incomplete, four choruses (Box-folder 118/2)
  - O bom Alvinho
    - Lead sheets; lyric sheets, Lyrics by Jane Duboc (Box-folder 23/8)
  - Octet for Sea Cliff
    - Score; parts (octet), On folder: Portofino variations; extra scores and parts, incomplete (Box-folder 107/1)
    - Score; parts (octet), On folder: Extra parts (Box-folder 108/1)
    - Score; parts (octet), On folder: Portofino variations; RCA recording date 3/2/89 (Box-folder 106/5)
    - Parts (octet) (Box-folder 107/3)
  - Off minor, Thelonious Monk
    - Sketch score; lead sheet, For Duke (Box-folder 137/2)
  - Off second, Sy Johnson
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band) (Box-folder 28/2)
  - Oh, Mr. Sauter? Yes, Mr. Finegan
    - Score; sketches; parts, For the 1995 recording Dragonfly (Box-folder 140/14)
    - Part (piano), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 114)
    - Part (bass, drums), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 115)
    - Lead sheet, On folder: New songs for quartet 2-9-93 (Box-folder 23/12)
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 23/10)
  - Ohio traveler
    - Lead sheet, On folder: New quartet, 6/24/94 (Box-folder 23A/1)
  - Old friends, Pedro Iturralde
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 8/1)
  - On the road with me
    - Lead sheets; lyric notes, On folder: Make new print for Mel Tormé (Box-folder 21/1)
  - On the wild side
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 17/1)
  - On this morning we wed
    - Lead sheet; lyric note (Box-folder 20/19)
    - Lead sheet, For the Mel Tormé vocal compilation "Tentet with Tormé" (Box-folder 62/6)
  - Once, in Hollywood
    - Lead sheet, On folder: New songs for quartet 2/9/93, originals (Box-folder 23/12)
  - One cloudy day
    - Lead sheets, From recording session with Dave Grusin (Box-folder 15/5)
  - One more time, Barry Manilow
    - Lead sheet; parts (vocal, baritone saxophone) (Box-folder 19/4)
  - One to ten in Ohio
    - Score; parts (Concert Jazz Band) (Box-folder 135/1)
    - Lead sheet; percussion part (Box-folder 9/3)
  - Ontet
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 10/5)
  - Open country, Bob Brookmeyer
    - Parts, Incomplete; Bob Brookmeyer arrangement (Box-folder 8/4)
  - Opener
    - Parts (alto saxophone 2, tenor saxophone 1), From "Shorty Rogers" folder (Box-folder 62/2)
  - Originale #1, Gary McFarland
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 8/3)
  - The other side of the Sun
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 18/8)
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 18/10)
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 23A/14)
  - Out back of the barn
    - Score; parts (Concert Jazz Band) (Box-folder 25/3)
    - Part (bass), GM personal performance part (Box-folder 116)
    - Parts, On folder: Quartet turmpet parts - originals (Box-folder 66/7)
    - Part (piano), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 114)
    - Part (bass, drums), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 115)
    - Lead sheets (Box-folder 13/9)
  - Out of a golden notebook
    - Score (Box-folder 13/9)
    - Sketches, From "Misc. works, some for Count Basie Band" folder (Box-folder 19/3)
  - Out of the past, Benny Golson
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 8/2)
  - Out of the way of the people
    - Part (baritone saxophone part), From "Brubeck parts" folder (Box-folder 82/1)
  - Out of this world, Harold Arlen / Johnny Mercer
    - Score; parts (Concert Jazz Band), Bill Holman arrangement (Box-folder 119/5)
  - Over the hill and out of the woods
    - Score; parts (Box-folder 134/1)
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band) (Box-folder 40/6)
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 9/2)
  - P.S. I love you, Julian Lee arrangement for the 1965 recording Feelin' good
    - Score (strings) (Box-folder 117/5)
    - Parts (strings) (Box-folder 4/4)
    - Parts (strings) (Box-folder 5/3)
  - Paganini in perpetuo
    - Score; part (baritone saxophone) (orchestra), On folder: Rochester Phil., 5/19-20/1989, arr. John Dankworth; Laid in: program and notes (Box-folder 144/4)
  - Parade, Other title: Paradise one
    - Part (trumpet), From "Small band trumpet parts" folder (Box-folder 66/2)
    - Lead sheet; part (trumpet) (Box-folder 12/6)
  - Parade samba, Other title: Paraiso
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 18/8)
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 24/2)
    - Lead sheets with lyrics; parts (baritone saxophone), For the 1994 recording Paraiso (Box-folder 23/8)
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 23A/7)
  - Paradise cafe, Barry Manilow
    - Lead sheet; parts (piano, bass, baritone saxophone) (Box-folder 19/4)
  - Parallelo
    - Lead sheet, On folder: New songs for quartet, 2-9-93, originals (Box-folder 23/12)
  - Park Avenue petite, Benny Golson
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 8/2)
  - The party's over, Styne/Comden/Green
    - Score (big band), For the recording Holliday with Mulligan (Box-folder 145/6)
    - Parts (piano, bass), For Buffington Memorial Service, Bernie Leighton (piano), Chet Amsterdam (bass), July 22, 1981 (Box-folder 13/8)
    - Parts (big band), For the recording Holliday with Mulligan (Box-folder 1/6)
  - Pass the peace pipe, Roger Edens/Ralph Blane/Hugh Martin; For the recording Holliday with Mulligan
    - Score (Concert Jazz Band) (Box-folder 145/2)
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band) (Box-folder 3/2)
  - Peaceful in the country
    - Sketch (Box-folder 52/1)
  - Pebbles
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 23/3)
    - Lead sheet, On folder: New quartet, 6/24/94 (Box-folder 23A/1)
  - Penthouse groove, Terry Gibbs
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 24/3)
  - Perdido, Duke Ellington
    - Parts (alto saxophone, tenor saxophone), From "Shorty Rogers" folder (Box-folder 62/2)
  - Phoenix burning
    - Lead sheet, On folder: New songs for quartet, 2-9-93 (Box-folder 23/12)
  - Piano blues
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 10/5)
  - Piece for jazz bassoon and orchestra, Henry Mancini
    - Conductor's score; part (bassoon) (Box-folder 81/5)
  - Piper 2
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 24/3)
  - Pipper, Ed Finckel
    - Score; parts (Concert Jazz Band) (Box-folder 118/6)
  - Planta Genestra
    - Sketch score, For CBS (Box-folder 14/1)
  - Players
    - Sketches, From "Misc. works, some for Count Basie Band" folder (Box-folder 19/3)
  - Please don't talk about me when I'm gone, Sam H. Stept
    - Score (masters), Julian Lee arrangement (Box-folder 142/4)
    - Score (strings), Julian Lee arrangement (Box-folder 4/11)
    - Parts (strings, rhythm) (Box-folder 90/2)
    - Parts (orchestra), On folder: Working parts as of 6/28/1986 (Box-folder 95/1)
    - Parts (strings), Julian Lee arrangement (Box-folder 4/10)
    - Part (bass), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 115)
  - Plenty of nothin'
    - Parts (baritone saxophone, bass, piano), GM personal performance parts (Box-folder 116)
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band, no rhythm parts) (Box-folder 46/4)
  - Pola
    - Lead sheet, On folder: New songs for quartet 2-9-93, originals (Box-folder 23/12)
  - Polka dots and moonbeams, Jimmy Van Heusen
    - Score (Concert Jazz Band), Bob Brookmeyer arrangement (Box-folder 145/9)
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band), On folder: Claude Thornhill, the lost tunes, rec'd from Ken Poston 7/95 (Box-folder 47/2)
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band), Bob Brookmeyer arrangement (Box-folder 32/3)
  - Poor little rich girl
    - Score (big band), Transcription by Mark Lopeman (Box-folder 130/5)
  - Port of Baltimore blues
    - Part (piano), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 114)
    - Part (bass, drums), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 115)
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 19/12)
    - Lead sheet, From studio session with Scott Hamilton for the recording Soft lights and sweet music (Box-folder 19/17)
  - The portrait, Benny Golson
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 8/2)
  - Prelude in E minor, Frederick Chopin
    - Parts (rhythm only) (Box-folder 67/1)
    - Lead sheet, On folder: GM tunes/lead sheets, returned by Dave Brubeck, May 1984 (Box-folder 82/2)
  - Prelude to a gentle lion
    - Sketch score; parts (tentet), Trumpet 1 part is missing; At top of score: Birthday annagram for E. Ellington (Box-folder 145/19)
    - Parts, Titled "Prelude to a kiss." These parts were probably arranged for the 1969 performance at the White House, "Tribute to Duke Ellington" (Box-folder 58/10)
  - Pretty little Gypsy, Gary McFarland
    - Score (Concert Jazz Band), Gary McFarland arrangement (Box-folder 121/9)
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band), Gary McFarland arrangement (Box-folder 29/1)
    - Lead sheet, Gary McFarland arrangement (Box-folder 8/3)
  - Queensnboro bridge
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 18/3)
  - Queer street, Count Base/Jimmy Mundy
    - Parts (Box-folder 59/4)
  - Rain, rain go away, Vince Guaraldi
    - Parts (quartet), On folder: Recording 6/16/89 A and R studios (Box-folder 22/9)
  - The raven
    - Lead sheet, On folder: New quartet, 6/24/94 (Box-folder 23A/1)
  - Ray-O
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 24/4)
  - Ready and able
    - Lead sheets, From "Kai Winding" folder (Box-folder 8/8)
  - The real thing
    - Score; parts (Concert Jazz Band), Richard DeRosa arrangement (Box-folder 126/6)
    - Part (piano), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 114)
    - Part (bass, drums), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 115)
    - Lead sheets; notes (Box-folder 15/9)
    - Lead sheets (Box-folder 16/1)
    - Lead sheet, For the Mel Tormé vocal compilation "Tentet with Tormé" (Box-folder 62/6)
    - Sketches, On folder: Arrangement for Q, Telarc recording (Box-folder 64/4)
  - Reconsidering again
    - Lead sheet, On folder: New songs for quartet 2/9/93, originals (Box-folder 23/12)
  - Recuerdo
    - Parts (baritone saxophone), From "Brubeck parts" folder (Box-folder 82/1)
  - The red door, Zoot Sims/Gerry Mulligan
    - Parts (big band) (Box-folder 50/4)
    - Part (piano), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 114)
    - Part (bass), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 115)
  - Regeneration, Rayburn Wright
    - Parts (baritone saxophone), On folder: Wilder winds concert, bari saxophone solo parts (Box-folder 81/4)
  - Remember
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band), Bob Donovan arrangement (Box-folder 28/3)
  - Repetition, Neal Hefti
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 8/11)
  - Reunion
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 11/2)
  - Revelation
    - Score (octet), Bill Holman arrangement (Box-folder 135/7)
    - Parts, On folder: Saxes arr. "Mulligan Songbook" album (originals) (Box-folder 56/3)
    - Lead sheet, Criterion Music Corp. (Box-folder 10/5)
  - Rhapsody for baritone saxophone
    - Score; part (solo saxophone), Mark Watters arrangement (Box-folder 90/4)
  - Richard's tune, Simon Pilbrow
    - Lead sheet, Note in GM's music library: Some good tunes from an Australian (Box-folder 22/24)
  - Ring around a bright star
    - Score; lead sheet, On folder: Carriage House date 3/15/89 (Box-folder 22/2)
    - Part (piano), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 114)
    - Part (bass, drums), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 115)
  - Rio one
    - Part (baritone saxophone) (Box-folder 24/2)
    - Lead sheet; "saxophone overdubs" (Box-folder 12/6)
    - Lead sheets (Box-folder 23/8)
    - Lead sheets, From "Brasilian collection" folder (Box-folder 18/8)
    - Lead sheet, Note in GM's music library: Mulligan tunes given to Sergio Bardotti (Box-folder 19/8)
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 23A/8)
  - Robin's nest
    - Score; parts (Concert Jazz Band), On folder: Claude Thornhill, the lost tunes, rec'd from Ken Poston 7/95 (Box-folder 47/3)
  - Rock salt
    - Parts (miscellaneous) (Box-folder 160/4)
  - Rocker
    - Score; parts (tentet), On folder: Parts, orig copy and transposed parts, score, new tentet (Box-folder 145/17)
    - Sketch; parts (Concert Jazz Band) (Box-folder 28/5)
    - Part (piano) (Box-folder 10/3)
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band) (Box-folder 66/5)
    - Parts (tentet) (Box-folder 111/4)
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 10/9)
    - Sketch, On folder: First sketches for tentet album (Box-folder 66/4)
  - Rocker suite
    - Parts (masters) (Box-folder 78/1)
    - Parts (orchestra) (Box-folder 78/3)
    - Parts (orchestra), 3rd movement only; Tom Fey arrangement (Box-folder 78/4)
  - Rose of the Rio Grande
    - Score (big band), On folder: Mark Lopeman transcription (Box-folder 130/6)
    - Score; parts (Concert Jazz Band), Score and parts from original version found at UNT, 2/95 (Box-folder 46/5)
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band), On folder: Claude Thornhill, the lost tunes, rec'd from Ken Poston 7/95 (Box-folder 47/1)
  - Rouge
    - Score, Note in GM's music library: John Lewis score (Box-folder 62/7)
    - Parts (tentet) (Box-folder 112/4)
  - Round about midnight
    - Score; parts (Concert Jazz Band), Incomplete (Box-folder 126/4)
    - Parts (bass), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book, titled "Around midnight" (Box-folder 115)
  - Round about sundown
    - Score; parts (Concert Jazz Band), Incomplete (Box-folder 124/1)
    - Parts (bass, drums), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book, titled "Around sundown" (Box-folder 115)
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 17/3)
  - Round and round, Lee Konitz
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 23A/6)
  - Ruby my dear, Thelonious Monk
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 24/5)
  - The run home
    - Lead sheet with annotations, On folder: Art Farmer, Lincoln Center '94, The art of trumpet (Box-folder 24/1)
  - Salt peanuts
    - Part (alto saxophone), Chic O'Farrill arrangement (Box-folder 58/7)
  - Samba La Rue
    - Lead sheet, On folder: GM parts, Kelly and Mike's tunes (Box-folder 67/7)
  - San Remo tunes for Sergio Nanni
    - Lead sheets (Box-folder 21/2)
  - (Theme from) Sandpiper
    - Score (strings) (Box-folder 117/5)
    - Parts (strings) (Box-folder 4/2)
  - Sandy, with a brand new smile
    - Score; parts (trumpet, woodwinds) (Concert Jazz Band), Score has 1st chorus only (Box-folder 118/1)
  - Sandy at the beach
    - Sketches for solo saxophone (Box-folder 38/4)
    - Score; sketches (Concert Jazz Band) (Box-folder 127/1)
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 16/11)
  - Sapito, Other title: Zapito
    - Parts (bass, drums), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 115)
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 11/4)
    - Lead sheet (Synclavier) (Box-folder 20/3)
    - Lead sheet, On folder: GM tunes/lead sheets, returned by Dave Brubeck, May 1984 (Box-folder 82/2)
  - Saratoga Spring
    - Lead sheet; parts (trumpet, bass), Record date with Grusin (Box-folder 15/5)
  - Satin doll, Duke Ellington
    - Score; parts (baritone saxophone, alto saxophone, trumpet, rhythm), Arrangement for three horns (Box-folder 21/6)
    - Score; parts (tentet) (Box-folder 138/7)
    - Score; parts (tentet) (Box-folder 113/9)
    - Parts (alto saxophone, trombone parts) (Box-folder 68/1)
    - Parts; sketch of saxophone 5 part (Concert Jazz Band), Note: Old parts, version 2 (Box-folder 41/3)
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band), Revised parts, 1986 February 6 (Box-folder 41/2)
    - Part (piano), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 114)
    - Part (bass, drums), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 115)
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 16/7)
  - Sax and Mozart minor, Earlier title: Festive minor
    - Score (orchestra) (Box-folder 142/6)
    - Parts (orchestra), On folder: Formerly "Festive minor," playing parts as of the Nat. Symph. 6/13/86 (Box-folder 84/2)
    - Parts (orchestra), On folder: Wworking parts as of 6/28/86; Laid in: Australian Pops Orch parts list, 3/1/1989 (Box-folder 90/5)
    - Parts (orchestra), On folder: Working parts as of 6/28/86 (Box-folder 101/16)
  - Sax and the rite of Igor, Earlier title: For an unfinished woman
    - Score (orchestra), On folder: The sax chronicles (Box-folder 143/5)
    - Parts (orchestra), On folder: Working parts as of 6/28/1986 (Box-folder 94/1)
    - Parts (orchestra), On folder: Formerly "For an unfinished woman," Nat. Symph. 6/13/1986 (Box-folder 87/2)
    - Parts (orchestra), On folder: Working parts as of 6/28/1986 (Box-folder 103/2)
    - Parts (orchestra), On folder: Working parts as of 6/28/1986 (Box-folder 103/1)
  - Sax chronicles
    - Parts, On folder: Extra parts not sent to Munich (Box-folder 94/2)
  - Sax in Debussy's garden
    - Score (orchestra), On folder: Formerly "Waltz sequence" (Box-folder 143/2)
    - Parts (orchestra), On folder: Formerly "Willows," Nat. Symph. 6/13/1986 (Box-folder 86/1)
    - Parts (orchestra) (Box-folder 92/1)
    - Parts (orchestra) (Box-folder 102/1)
  - Sax on the Bach stairs
    - Score (orchestra), On folder: The sax chronicles; Note in GM's music library: Formerly "Sun on the stairs" (Box-folder 142/5)
    - Parts (orchestra) (Box-folder 91/2)
    - Parts (orchestra), On folder: Formerly "Sun on the stairs," playing parts as of the Nat. Symph. 6/13/1986 (Box-folder 85/1)
    - Parts (orchestra) (Box-folder 101/3)
  - Sax on the Rhine, Earlier title: Grand tour
    - Score (orchestra) (Box-folder 143/4)
    - Parts (orchestra), On folder: Working parts as of 6/28/1986 (Box-folder 102/2)
    - Parts (orchestra), On folder: Formerly "Grand tour," Nat. Symph. 6/13/86 (Box-folder 86/2)
  - Sax und der Rosenkavalier, Earlier title: Waltz sequence
    - Parts (orchestra), On folder: Formerly "Waltz sequence," Nat. Symph. 6/13/86 (Box-folder 87/1)
    - Parts (orchestra), Laid in: Australian Pops Orchestra parts list (Box-folder 103/1)
    - Parts (orchestra) (Box-folder 143/3)
  - Say no more, Barry Manilow
    - Lead sheet; parts (piano, baritone saxophone) (Box-folder 19/4)
  - Scrapple from the Apple, Charlie Parker
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 17/7)
  - The second time around, Jimmy Van Heusen / Sammy Cahn
    - Score (strings), Julian Lee arrangement for the 1965 recording Feelin' good (Box-folder 117/5)
    - Parts (strings), Julian Lee arrangement for the 1965 recording Feelin' good (Box-folder 5/2)
    - Parts (strings), For the 1965 recording Feelin' good (Box-folder 4/1)
    - Parts, Note in GM's music library: Music from record dates (Box-folder 53/4)
  - See here, Svengali
    - Sketch score; parts (big band), On folder: Some original sketches for John Dankworth Orch. (Box-folder 55/4)
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 11/1)
  - Seneca scene
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band), Bob Freeman arrangement (Box-folder 28/3)
  - Sextet
    - Score (octet), On folder: "Songbook" album, saxophone section scores by Bill Holman (Box-folder 135/7)
    - Parts, On folder: Saxes arr. "Mulligan Songbook" album (Box-folder 56/7)
  - The shadow of your smile
    - Score (tentet), Dated: Aug. 21, '66 (Box-folder 136/2)
    - Parts (tentet), On folder: For Gil Evans "Big tentet" (Box-folder 65/1)
  - Shine, John Eardley
    - Sketch scores, On folder: For bari and trumpet (Box-folder 145/16)
  - Shinjuku gate
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 19/5)
  - A silent mood
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band) (Box-folder 43/2)
  - Silver's serenade
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band), Ed Comer arrangement (Box-folder 49/4)
  - Simba
    - Score (Concert Jazz Band), On folder: Scored for Kenton 1/21/1952 (Box-folder 132/6)
    - Score (Concert Jazz Band), On folder: Original score, outchoruses only (Box-folder 139/6)
    - Score (tentet), On folder: Original score, outchoruses only (Box-folder 139/6)
    - Score; parts (Concert Jazz Band), On folder: Sketches of original score put together by Gunther Schuller, parts transcribed by Gunther Schuller, 6/95 (Box-folder 66/3)
    - Lead sheet, On folder: Misc. sextet parts (Box-folder 19/1)
    - Sketch, On folder: First sketches for tentet album (Box-folder 66/4)
  - Simple life, Bob Brookmeyer
    - Parts, Incomplete (Box-folder 8/4)
  - Six flats unfurnished, Dick Maltby
    - Parts (big band), Dick Maltby arrangement (Box-folder 59/5)
  - Sketch-orks, Vol. 1 and Vol. 2
    - Printed parts, Designed for small groups; transcribed from original recordings (Box-folder 17/12)
  - Sleepytime down South
    - Sketch score, On folder: Rochester Phil., 5/19-20/1989, arranger John Dankworth; Laid in: program and notes (Box-folder 144/4)
  - Smiles
    - Score (big band), On folder: Arr. GM, 1944 (Box-folder 131/1)
  - The snow queen
    - Lead sheets, Lyrics by Marty Brill (Box-folder 18/16)
  - Snowfall
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band), On folder: Claude Thornhill, the lost tunes, rec'd from Ken Poston 7/95 (Box-folder 47/2)
  - So nice, Bob Brookmeyer
    - Parts, Incomplete (Box-folder 8/4)
  - Sob a estrela
    - Lead sheets; lyric sheets, For the 1994 recording Paraiso (Box-folder 23/8)
  - Soft lights and sweet music, Irving Berlin
    - Part (drums), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 115)
    - Lead sheet, From studio session with Scott Hamilton for the recording Soft lights and sweet music (Box-folder 19/17)
  - Soft shoe
    - Part (piano), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 114)
    - Part (bass), From the Gerry Mulligan Quartet road book (Box-folder 115)
    - Lead sheets; rhythm parts (Box-folder 10/9)
  - Softly as I leave you
    - Percussion part, For the 1965 recording Feelin' good (Box-folder 4/3)
  - Somebody else's dream
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 17/5)
  - Someone to watch over me, George Gershwin
    - Score (Concert Jazz Band), Incomplete (Box-folder 118/4)
    - Parts (Concert Jazz Band), Incomplete (Box-folder 50/5)
  - Something borrowed, something blue
    - Lead sheets; sketches, From "Misc. parts from album with Zoot" folder (Box-folder 15/3)
  - Something for Sidney, Don Nelson
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 19/8)
  - Sometimes I'm happy
    - Score (big band), GM arrangement for Claude Thornhill, 1947 October 6 (Box-folder 146/5)
  - Son of a Godchild
    - Sketch, On folder: New intros in progress (Box-folder 140/7)
  - Song folk
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 24/4)
  - Song for Johnny Hodges
    - Lead sheet (Box-folder 17/1)
  - Song for Strayhorn
    - Score; parts (Concert Jazz Band), C83A parts for Johnny Dankworth Orchestra (Box-folder 124/4)
    - Score; parts (big band), Scored for "Jazz Gala," January 1976, West Germany (Box-folder 49/1)